<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="affirmations_array">
        <item>This too shall pass</item>
        <item>Just be</item>
        <item>You don’t have to control your thoughts. You just have to stop letting them control you.</item>
        <item>It is what it is</item>
        <item>You are right where you are supposed to be.</item>
        <item>Life isn’t that happens to you, it’s how you react to what happens to you.</item>
        <item>This too shall pass</item>
        <item>Nothing good gets away</item>
        <item>Whatever it takes, be yourself</item>
        <item>Think of your best self and show up as them</item>
        <item>Small smart decisions</item>
        <item>What has been is not what will be</item>
        <item>I am present in this moment, and this moment is enough</item>
        <item>Breathe in peace, exhale stress</item>
        <item>I am calm, centered, and focused</item>
        <item>May I be kind to myself and others</item>
        <item>I am grateful for this moment and all it offers</item>
        <item>I let go of worries and trust in the universe</item>
        <item>With each breath, I become more relaxed and at ease</item>
        <item>I am a peaceful presence in the world</item>
        <item>I accept what is and let go of what was</item>
        <item>I choose to let go of negativity and embrace positivity</item>
        <item>I am here, now, fully present and engaged</item>
        <item>With every breath, I release tension and find peace</item>
        <item>I trust in the wisdom of my body and mind</item>
        <item>I am grateful for the small things in life that bring me joy</item>
        <item>I let go of the past and embrace the present moment</item>
        <item>I am open to the beauty and wonder of the world around me</item>
        <item>I am at peace with myself and those around me</item>
        <item>I am mindful of my thoughts, emotions, and actions</item>
        <item>I trust in the journey of life and where it\'s taking me</item>
        <item>I am grounded and rooted in the present moment</item>
        <item>I am enough, just as I am</item>
        <item>I cultivate patience and understanding with myself and others</item>
        <item>I let go of judgments and embrace compassion</item>
        <item>I am grateful for the lessons that come from each experience</item>
        <item>I am calm and centered in the midst of chaos</item>
        <item>I trust in my intuition and inner wisdom</item>
        <item>I am open to change and growth</item>
        <item>I focus on my breath and allow my thoughts to pass</item>
        <item>I am kind to myself and practice self-compassion</item>
        <item>I am mindful of my surroundings and the beauty of nature</item>
        <item>I embrace the uncertainty of life with a sense of adventure</item>
        <item>I find peace in the present moment, free from worry and anxiety</item>
        <item>I am aware of my feelings and choose to respond with kindness and understanding</item>
        <item>I am grateful for the abundance of love and support in my life</item>
        <item>I trust in the process of life and the journey it takes me on</item>
        <item>I am free from attachment to outcomes and trust in the flow of life</item>
        <item>I find joy and beauty in simple moments</item>
        <item>I am centered and grounded in my own inner peace</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>