<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="affirmations_array">
        <item>I am worthy of love and respect.</item>
        <item>I am capable of achieving my goals.</item>
        <item>I trust my intuition and make wise decisions.</item>
        <item>I am strong and resilient.</item>
        <item>I am grateful for everything in my life.</item>
        <item>I believe in myself and my abilities.</item>
        <item>I radiate positivity and attract good things.</item>
        <item>I am confident in my unique talents and skills.</item>
        <item>I am deserving of happiness and success.</item>
        <item>I am surrounded by supportive and loving people.</item>
        <item>I am in control of my thoughts and emotions.</item>
        <item>I forgive myself and others easily.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of abundance and prosperity.</item>
        <item>I am constantly improving and growing.</item>
        <item>I am at peace with myself and my past.</item>
        <item>I am always learning and expanding my knowledge.</item>
        <item>I am grateful for my body and treat it with kindness.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of respect and admiration.</item>
        <item>I trust the universe to guide me towards my path.</item>
        <item>I am open to new opportunities and experiences.</item>
        <item>I am free of negative self-talk and limiting beliefs.</item>
        <item>I am grateful for my unique qualities and personality.</item>
        <item>I am kind and compassionate towards myself and others.</item>
        <item>I am confident in my ability to handle challenges.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of love and affection.</item>
        <item>I am successful in all areas of my life.</item>
        <item>I am living my best life.</item>
        <item>I am constantly attracting positive energy.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of achieving my dreams.</item>
        <item>I am proud of my accomplishments.</item>
        <item>I am surrounded by abundance and prosperity.</item>
        <item>I am confident in my ability to achieve my goals.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of respect and admiration.</item>
        <item>I am grateful for the challenges that make me stronger.</item>
        <item>I am surrounded by positive and supportive people.</item>
        <item>I am a magnet for good things.</item>
        <item>I am in charge of my own happiness.</item>
        <item>I am confident in my ability to create the life I want.</item>
        <item>I am grateful for my experiences and lessons learned.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of success and prosperity.</item>
        <item>I am loved unconditionally.</item>
        <item>I am patient and trust the timing of my life.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of trust and honesty from others.</item>
        <item>I am constantly improving my mindset and attitude.</item>
        <item>I am capable of overcoming any obstacle.</item>
        <item>I am grateful for the abundance in my life.</item>
        <item>I am confident in my own abilities and skills.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of respect and kindness from others.</item>
        <item>I am creating a life that brings me joy and fulfillment.</item>
        <item>I am at peace with my past and excited for my future.</item>
        <item>I am capable of achieving my dreams.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of love and affection from others.</item>
        <item>I am surrounded by positive and loving relationships.</item>
        <item>I am grateful for my inner strength and resilience.</item>
        <item>I am confident in my own beauty and worth.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of success and happiness.</item>
        <item>I am surrounded by opportunities for growth and learning.</item>
        <item>I am deserving of all the good things in life.</item>
        <item>I am constantly improving and evolving.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of kindness and compassion from others.</item>
        <item>I am grateful for my body and treat it with love.</item>
        <item>I am confident in my own creativity and imagination.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of trust and respect from others.</item>
        <item>I am living a life that reflects my values and passions.</item>
        <item>I am surrounded by abundance and prosperity.</item>
        <item>I am capable of achieving anything I set my mind to.</item>
        <item>I am grateful for the opportunities to learn and grow.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of love and respect.</item>
        <item>I am capable of achieving anything I set my mind to.</item>
        <item>I am strong, confident, and resilient.</item>
        <item>I choose to focus on the good in every situation.</item>
        <item>I am grateful for everything in my life.</item>
        <item>I trust in my abilities and instincts.</item>
        <item>I am surrounded by positive energy and love.</item>
        <item>I let go of negative thoughts and emotions.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of success and happiness.</item>
        <item>I radiate love and positivity wherever I go.</item>
        <item>I am blessed with abundance and prosperity.</item>
        <item>I am patient, kind, and compassionate towards myself and others.</item>
        <item>I am healthy, vibrant, and full of energy.</item>
        <item>I am proud of myself and my accomplishments.</item>
        <item>I forgive myself and others for past mistakes.</item>
        <item>I am at peace with myself and the world around me.</item>
        <item>I am in control of my thoughts and emotions.</item>
        <item>I am deserving of love, joy, and abundance.</item>
        <item>I trust that everything happens for a reason.</item>
        <item>I attract positive people and opportunities into my life.</item>
        <item>I am grateful for my body and all that it does for me.</item>
        <item>I am worthy of self-care and self-love.</item>
        <item>I am blessed with endless possibilities and opportunities.</item>
        <item>I am confident in my abilities and talents.</item>
        <item>I am open to learning and growth.</item>
        <item>I choose to see the beauty in everything and everyone.</item>
        <item>I am surrounded by abundance and prosperity.</item>
        <item>I am grateful for the present moment and all that it holds.</item>
        <item>I am loved, appreciated, and valued.</item>
        <item>I trust the journey of my life.</item>
        <item>I release all fear and embrace love.</item>
        <item>I am capable of overcoming any obstacle.</item>
        <item>I am filled with joy, peace, and gratitude</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>